PAFF：Wake up~Can you hear me?
PAFF：起きて　私の声が聞こえる？
PAFF：It's already been three months since everything happened.
PAFF：あれから3か月が経ったね  元気にしてるかな？
Leo：From the bottom of our hearts, we promise that from here on out,
PAFF：Vanessaが世界を危機に陥れてから
PAFF：After averting the crisis that Vanessa threatened the world with...
Leo：今後は秘密裏に古代文明を使用せず
PAFF：A.R.C. abolished the Library's facilities
PAFF：A.R.C.は Libraryの使用を廃止して
Leo：and will be transparent with all the content of our research
Leo：研究内容においても公開し
PAFF：and used other types of server technology to replace the operations of the virtual internet
PAFF：今は他のサーバー技術で  神経ネットワークを運営してる
Leo：by making it available to the public
Leo：透明性の高い経営を目指してまいります
Leo：Starting from today, we will implement serious changes to our internal structure
Leo：また、社内改革を行い
Leo：For the development of society and humanity
Leo：社会と人類の発展のために
PAFF：Of course, many people are unable to accept such a decision
PAFF：まだ現実を受け入れられない人もたくさんいる
Leo：we will seriously reconsider our position in society and the direction we are headed...
Leo：今一度経営方針を見直し……
PAFF：Especially those who lost their loved ones as a result of what happened
PAFF：特に愛する人を失った人たち……
PAFF：But after a period of time most people returned to their normal lives
PAFF：でも　ほとんどの人は  もう普段通りの生活を送ってる
PAFF：Time gradually diluted all that had occurred...
PAFF：こうやって時間と共に  全て忘れられていくんだね……
PAFF：After graduating from university, NEKO became a professional streamer musician
PAFF：NEKOはアカデミーを卒業してから  編曲や実況主の仕事をしてるよ
PAFF：Besides her normal content of music, games and random gossip
PAFF：音楽のことからゲームやゴシップまで  幅広くやってるみたい
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Yo-ho! NEKO's here!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：やっほー！NEKO だよー！
PAFF：she also started a new series
PAFF：それに　新しく作ったチャンネルでは
PAFF：where she actively goes out to help the victims that were affected by the incident with Vanessa
PAFF：Vanessa事件で被害に遭った人たちを助ける活動をしているの
Victim：We don't need help from you internet addicts. Please, go away...
被害者：ネット中毒の人の助けはいらないんで  帰ってください……
PAFF：It's not easy, but she doesn't get discouraged
PAFF：大変そうだけど　気落ちすることもなく
PAFF：She used money she made from her music and streams to set up a foundation
PAFF：音楽と生放送で稼いだお金で  慈善団体を設立して
PAFF：that donates to the people affected and related illnesses
PAFF：被害に遭った人たちのために  募金活動とかもしてる
PAFF：At night, she's still a die-hard music fan
PAFF：そんなNEKOだけど  夜はただの音楽好きのNEKOのまま
PAFF：As for Xenon, he got back to performing with a band after everything was over
PAFF：Xenonはまたバンド活動を再開したよ
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Not bad~!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：おつー！
PAFF：Xenon's sister Shannon,
PAFF：Xenonの妹 Shannonちゃんは
PAFF：she gradually shed the effect that the virtual internet had on her
PAFF：あれから徐々に神経ネットワークの  影響を受けなくなって
PAFF：and her condition started to improve
PAFF：病状もよくなってきてる
PAFF：A.R.C. kept begging Xenon to return
PAFF：A.R.C.は Xenonに帰ってきてほしいみたい
PAFF：But no matter how generous their offers were, no matter what position they promised
PAFF：でも  どんなにいい待遇や役職を用意しても
PAFF：Xenon refused to accept
PAFF：Xenonは一向に応える気配はなさそう
PAFF：Perhaps in his heart,
PAFF：彼の心の中には振り切らない限り  前に進めない過去があるんだろうね
PAFF：After the dissolution of Baro,
PAFF：バローが瓦解した後
PAFF：the position of JOE's bar in the inner circles grew higher and higher
PAFF：JOEのバーは  その世界の中でどんどん地位が上がって
PAFF：JOE became more and more like Uncle Saxon
PAFF：JOEもだんだん叔父さんである  Saxonさんのようになってきたよ
PAFF：and some familiar faces could be seen hanging around, just like before
PAFF：お店には　見慣れた顔がいる
PAFF：Mr. Neumann decided to move to Node 13,
PAFF：Neumannさんは  Node13に移住することに決めて
PAFF：continuing to research the unsolved mysteries of his ancestors with Sasha
PAFF：Sashaさんは引き続きまだ解けていない
PAFF：Humanity's interest in ancient technology didn't disappear
PAFF：人類の古代文明に対する好奇心はまだ失せてない
PAFF：and missions of A.R.C.'s Exploration Team continued
PAFF：A.R.C.の探査隊もいまだに任務は続けてる
PAFF：Occasionally, they run into someone with motives different from their own
PAFF：その途中で　たまに目的の違う人に  遭遇したりもするみたい
ConneR：Oh? You again?
ConneR：なんだね？君か？
ConneR：Keep up the hard work
ConneR：ご苦労様
PAFF：Rin was able to break free of A.R.C.'s control,
PAFF：Rinは A.R.C.のコントロール下から解放されて
PAFF：concealing her Architect identity and living with Sagar
PAFF：アーキテクトであることを隠しながら  Sagarと暮らしてる
PAFF：She also returned to Node 03 to look for her past memories
PAFF：そんな彼女もNode03で  過去の記憶の手掛かりを探してるみたい
Rin：Ah! Oh...
Rin：わっ！あ……
Rin：I'm s-so sorry!
Rin：ご、ごめんなさい！
Rin：Wah!
Rin：きゃっ！
Daigo：Chief, here's the part you asked for
Daigo：リーダーお探しの部品です
PAFF：Last time we heard from Nora
PAFF：最後にNoraの情報が入ってきた時には
Nora：Thank you, just put it there
Nora：ありがとう　そこに置いておいて
PAFF：she was just about finished repairing ROBO_Head
PAFF：もうROBO_Headの修理が  終わりそうだって言ってた
Nora："NORA"
Nora：「NORA」
PAFF：Then... there's me
PAFF：そして……私
PAFF：Once again, I returned to the stage as PAFF as well as doing performances on the street
PAFF：私は　またPAFFとして  ステージと路上で歌ってる
PAFF：I accepted the fact that I was both Aroma and Kaori...
PAFF：自分がAromaであり  薫である事実を受け入れたんだ……
PAFF：We... are PAFF
PAFF：PAFFは　私たち
PAFF：Though I don't know what the future holds for humanity now that Vanessa is gone
PAFF：Vanessaが消えて  人類の未来がどうなるのかはまだ分からない
PAFF：we're going to continue to use music to give power and courage to everyone
PAFF：私たちが音楽でみんなに与えられるパワーは  勇気は
PAFF：It may not be much
PAFF：ほんの少しだけかもしれない
PAFF：but we'll try to use everything in our power to change this world,
PAFF：でもこの世界を変えるために全力を尽くすよ
PAFF：because that's all we can do
PAFF：それが私たちにできる唯一のことだから
PAFF：This... is our story.
PAFF：これが、私たちの物語